so now let's try to apply the concept
that we have learned to an actual cache
we know that the main memory in a
computer is large and very slow to
access compared to processor speed and
also we know that there is lots of
spatial and temporal locality present in
our data accesses most programs exhibit
a lot of spatial and temporal locality
so for an access to a memory location
what do you think we should do should we
go to the main memory for every access
should we have a small memory inside the
processor core and then we bring stuff
we access there so that next time we
need it we can find it quickly or should
we have a huge memory next to our
processor chip because it won't fit on
the processor chip and then as we read
from the main memory we bring everything
into this memory that is next to us